<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resources on Gossip</title><link>https://gossip.rest/docs/resources/</link><description>Recent content in Resources on Gossip</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://gossip.rest/docs/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cases</title><link>https://gossip.rest/docs/resources/cases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gossip.rest/docs/resources/cases/</guid><description>This page needs to be moved to the API Reference, and rewritten according to the new route standards Cases are actions tied to a specific user.
They include some standardised properties as well as permitting for some freeform data to be stored in JSON format.
A case object looks like the following:
Field Type Description id snowflake The unique identifier for this case app_id snowflake The application which created this case type string The type of case target_id snowflake The identifier of the targeted user target_name string The name of the targeted user mod_id snowflake Unique identifier for the moderator who created this case mod_name string Name of the moderator who created this case detail string Free-form (and human-readable) description of the case expires int?</description></item><item><title>API Reference</title><link>https://gossip.rest/docs/resources/api-reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gossip.rest/docs/resources/api-reference/</guid><description>Authentication There are two modes of authentication for routes in Gossip:
Header-based authentication using the Authorization header. No authentication; anonymous requests. Header-based Authentication For authenticated endpoints the client should pass an Authorization header with their bearer token:
Authorization: Bearer b3c98d3f Rate Limits Content TBD Routes The basic route format for API routes is /{version}/{topic}/{resource}. All routes detailed below assume that /{version} is used as the base URL and hence does not include that.</description></item></channel></rss>